JULY 15TH (THURS) 10:43 AM
Now who is this? I've never
seen this man in my life.
Good afternoon.
I'm Kinoto, the architect.
I believe you called me earlier.
I'm here to give an assessment of
the fire restoration
and renovation.
That's right. We did agree to meet.
Heaven's Door!
My apologies for
the forceful greeting,
but I've reason to be cautious.
YES! THIS GIG'S IN THE BAG!
TIME TO MAKE SOME MONEY!
ROHAN KISHIBE MUST BE LOADED.
I'M GONNA MAKE A KILLING.
I'll JUST CHARGE A LITTLE BIT MORE
AND HOPE HE BITES.
Born in 1970, top notch architect.
Name, Masazo Kinoto.
I see.
He's definitely the man I called.
Nothing points to him being
a Stand user or enemy.
Hm?
I HATE IT WHEN PEOPLE
LOOK AT MY BACK.
I REALLY DON'T WANT ANYONE
PEEKING AT MY BACK.
IT'S NOT LIKE I HAVE ZITS OR
WEIRD SCARS OR A TATTOO,
I JUST DON'T WANT ANYBODY
LOOKING AT MY BACK!
I CAN'T GET A GIRLFRIEND.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?!
None of this makes any sense,
then again,
no one's without their own
bizarre fears and phobias.
Well, he seems safe enough
to let in the house.
That Rosham-boy seemed
pretty innocent, too…
In any case, a simple,
I can't attack Rohan, can't hurt.
Huh? I didn't just make
a major faux pas did I?
No. Please, come in. Let's talk.
Something wrong?
You'll find most of the fire damage
in the room facing the yard.
You can't perform an assessment
standing out there.
Oh, no, you should go ahead.
I'll follow behind.
Huh?
Now, please, go ahead.
JULY 15TH (THURS) 9:06 AM
EPISODE 32
JULY 15TH (THURS), PART 2
You know,
my escape couldn't be easier.
You fools still haven't figured out
where Yoshikage Kira went, have you?
You don't even know
what I look like.
You never thought my name
was just a little fishy?
You do know
it's Toyohiro Kanedaichi.
W-What the hell?
You're wearing some kind of mask?
I didn't only think about
leaving this thing…
I planned for a clean escape.
Well, I suppose I should
bid you sayonara.
Y-You piece of—
Please stay outside, Mr. Josuke.
I will remain here,
within this tower.
What?!
What the hell's gotten into you?
We're in this situation
because I discovered the tower.
I'm like this now because I decided
to transform into the power line
and climb to this position here.
I wanted you to think I was useful.
I wanted to change your opinion,
for you to be proud of me.
Okuyasu did say to butt out.
I brought this upon myself.
Don't trouble yourselves
on my behalf.
If I imagine this as the interior
of a spaceship,
it actually feels quite roomy.
You're a weirdo,
and a brave one at that.
Though I really don't care
who stays here.
As long as I'm outta here,
I'm happy.
The rest is up to you fool—
Nope, you're the only one
setting up camp in this dump.
The only one delivering
the final "sayonara"
will be from us to you, buddy!
J-Josuke!
Y-You mother—
Thanks to you cutting this line,
I was able to fix it
and get myself up here.
You're amaz—
Mikitaka, give me about
ten seconds, okay?
After I hang this d-bag out to dry
and put him back in his cage
where he belongs,
I'll heal you
like nothing happened.
Don't fall, Josuke!
Of course I won't fall.
I may've said you're amazing,
but I misspoke.
What I should have said
is you're a total moron.
I was content simply
leaving this place.
It never crossed my mind
to kill any one of you…
But now I'm gonna have to
push you to your death
before I can make my getaway,
you idiot!
Shut the hell up!
Shining Diamond…
Up close,
it's pretty damn impressive.
You really think
you stand a chance against me…
I can prance around the top of
this tower with my eyes closed.
I'm guessing its range
is about two meters.
What the hell!
Hey, dumb-ass!
You better cut that out!
Mr. Josuke,
I advise you to move, quickly!
He already slashed it
with his knife!
He already carved slits
into the beam!
That was a real low blow,
you know that!
But you're still not fast enough to
make my Shining Diamond sweat.
What are you smirking at,
you jungle gym freak?
Can't wait for the ass-whooping
I'm about to give you?!
I know every centimeter
of this tower
like the back of my hand.
I know exactly which angle to cut
to send the projectile
in exactly the direction I desire.
Like a pool shark who's bored
with his own mastery,
I know all the moves!
Pool shark?
Jo…
Josuke!
Not fast enough to make
Shining Diamond sweat, huh?
But do you know where
the projectiles are coming from?
Now how many more shots
did I fire off back there…
They're ricochetting off the beams
as I speak.
Here they come!
Mr. Josuke!
Behind you!
That's why I called you
a total moron.
That alien guy over there
at least had the balls
to say he'd stay behind.
You should have
just listened to him.
You could have lived.
B-Both of his arms?
There's no way he'll
be able to dodge another onslaught.
Now for the famous finishing blow!
- I think I'll aim for your…
- By the way, Okuyasu,
this guy's projectile thingies…
Did ya catch how many of them
I knocked back
with Shining Diamond?
Huh? Yeah, I saw.
You definitely got four of them.
What? What was that nonchalant
"by the way"?
Four of them, huh?
Well, that should be plenty.
Four shots should be
more than enough.
What are you idiots
blathering about?!
You mentioned the word ricochet.
That you ricocheted
your Stand's energy
like a bunch of billiard balls.
That's what you said.
Yeah, I did, what are you
gonna do about it, Josuke?!
My Stand's called Shining Diamond.
I'm guessing that old guy
in the photo told you,
it can correct destroyed matter
and fractured energy.
Correct…
Did I hear you say "correct"?
What the hell did you correct?!
Are you saying you had
the spare time
to correct something just now?
Come on, you're a fool!
He corrected the energy
ricocheting between the beams,
reversing its path so that it
returned to the slashed steel.
Mr. Josuke,
I thought you were done for,
but you had already won.
You're amazing…
I guess you didn't
misspoke after all,
you really do think I'm "amazing."
Please forgive me.
I only started living here
in this tower
to get away from other people.
But the older man in the photograph
said that as long as I could
trap a Stand user,
he'd make sure I could
have a life in the outside world,
so I decided to go for it…
Please! Will you be
so gracious as to let me
go back inside
the safety of the tower?
I never want to
have to leave again.
I just want to live out my life
between these beams.
I'll never contemplate
leaving this place ever again.
MORIOH LANDMARK NO. 9:
THE MAN IN THE ELECTRICAL TOWER
New Morioh landmark:
the man in the electrical tower.
He is a marvel of self-sufficiency,
but bring him
a bit of salt or snacks,
he'll be more than happy
to let you take a picture.
But be warned, he is timid.
He wears a mask and
will not divulge his real name.
I appreciate the confession,
but about the old guy
in the photograph…
Did he say anything else?
Like the whereabouts of his son,
Yoshikage Kira, or anything else?
Is there a Stand user named
Koichi here in Morioh?
What do you know about Koichi?!
Hey, take it easy,
the old guy and I were only
having a casual conversation,
he barely mentioned him.
I didn't think to ask anything,
and he didn't elaborate.
Well, what did he say
about Koichi?!
That he has eliminated him.
What?!
It seems the old guy
in the photograph
had already found his son,
Yoshikage Kira.
He said, from now on, he would
do more than just protect his son,
he said he would start
seeking out and attacking others.
Then he said a new Stand user
eliminated a Stand user
named Koichi just this morning…
That's all he said.
JULY 15TH (THURS) 10:58 AM
Hmm… This will be…
My goodness! Look at this door…
this will be about 800,000 yen!
And look at that,
it's designed in the vein of
either the Victorian
or Edwardian era!
It even uses
English-made materials…
This is going to be quite…
So he doesn't want anyone
looking a this back…
Maybe that explains
his odd behavior
when he first visited my home?
Here you go.
Oh, thank you.
Before it gets cold.
Oh, I'll be fine.
JULY 15TH (THURS) 11:16 AM
I must resist…
Now is not the time…
SHINING DIAMOND
JULY 15TH (THURS) 10:20 AM
I really hope they find
Koichi safe and sound…
JULY 15TH (THURS) 11:37 AM
Damn it! Where is he!
He's not at home, at school,
or any damn place!
Koichi! Koichi!
Where are you, Koichi?!
I'm not giving up!
I'll do whatever it takes, Koichi!
So that's the story.
With your scent-tracking ability,
I wanna know
if you'll help me find Koichi,
Yuya Fungami.
I'll get rid of your injuries,
that's the deal.
That's the deal?
I'm warning you,
don't mess with me, Josuke!
I don't play around!
I'll never forgive you
for doing this to me!
You think I, Yuya Fungami,
would sacrifice my pride
to help you?
So it is a no.
I knew it was a total long shot.
Well, see ya.
I'm kinda short on time.
Wait, huh?! So you're gonna
leave just like that?
W-Wait a second, hey!
Come on, you're not gonna
even give me a chance to bargain…
Okay, fine! I'll help you out!
Jeez, guess I don't really
have a choice…
Shit, I could hold out,
but then I'd just be stuck
in this dump even longer.
I can't give my girls
the kind of attention they deserve
while I'm like this,
for all I know they could be
on their way out,
I'm lonely and worried sick.
Besides, the accident
that got me into this whole mess
is my own doing,
I've got nothing against you.
Now can you hurry up and heal me?
These injuries are
driving me crazy!
Shining Diamond already
reversed your injuries.
Huh?
There's that face…
I am stunningly beautiful,
aren't I…
Beautiful as a Michelangelo
sculpture, at the very least.
But my eyes look
slightly droopy now…
Does your Stand
actually fix things 100%?
Count your blessings, prick!
Now, just how well does
your sense of smell work?
Let's see… I mean,
I can't promise you I'm as good
as some hunting dog or anything…
SNIFF
For example,
I can tell that three girls are
walking up the hall right now.
It smells like
Reiko, Akemi, and Yoshie.
They're my fan girls.
I can tell they're coming back
from the pachinko place.
Hey, Yu-babe! So?
Ah, Yu! Yu is out of bed!
Yo.
Yu baby, you're back…
Yu sweetie!
There, there,
my sweet little vixens.
So you're Josuke!
Why the hell're you here?
Want me to skewer you right here?
Enough. I hold no ill will
toward Josuke now.
Onto more important matters,
you gals just got back
from pachinko, correct?
Huh?
How did you know?
Cause, the part where your skirts
and asses touch reek of sweat.
Where else would you be
planting your cheeks down
on vinyl chairs for so long…
Akemi, got any chocolate?
You won at pachinko, right?
You're right! You're amazing, Yu.
Here, a little souvenir.
As you can see,
I am who I am thanks to them.
You helped me get back on my feet,
you have my support.
Not as good as some hunting dog?
You're a helluva lot better,
Yuya Fungami!
JULY 15TH (THURS) 12:05 PM
Is there something wrong, Sir?
The upstairs floor sustained
fire damage as well, right?
I'll perform the estimate,
so please go ahead.
What is this man doing?
What could be driving him to be
so obsessive about hiding his back?
If I see it, then what?
I have to see it!
How could I not want to
look at his back now!
If I have to trick him,
then so be it…
Oh, it itches… It itches…
If only I could reach it.
I suppose it would be rude
to ask a person I just met
to scratch it for me.
Well, I could help…
JULY 15TH (THURS) 12:28 PM
This is it.
This is where we found
Koichi's bag all by itself.
Koichi's house is less than
two minutes away.
How did this new Stand user storm
Koichi and snatch him
away from a busy school street?
No one saw him.
Josuke…
Our little deal doesn't
assume combat duty by me, correct?
Tracking only, correct?
I won't be fighting any enemies,
correct, Josuke?
Why are you asking me
those questions now?
You were already being tailed.
It's that man.
I smell Koichi's scent on that man.
He has something of Koichi's!
What? That bastard over there?
Wait! Come back here!
You bastard!
What did you do to Koichi?!
M-Mom?
Mom!
It's definitely my mom.
She's out cold, but alive.
I was watching from here,
and still haven't a clue…
When did he change into
Josuke's mom?
I heard Jotaro can stop time
for some two seconds,
but this is
a whole different level!
Even Jotaro wouldn't be able to
swap one person out
with another like that!
If he had just come out and hit me,
I would've been happy
just knocking him out…
But that bastard had to
go after my mom…
Scum like him must be punished!
This scheming scumbag
is gonna feel the pain!
Yuya! Where is the bastard?
Where's that piece of shit hiding?!
If you were touching him
and don't know,
then how would I know?
B-But the guy hasn't left, Josuke…
He's nearby. I can still smell him!
Hmm… Yuya Fungami, huh?
Who knew a simple nose
could work so well.
Well, at least originally,
I initiated my pursuit without
a single care of being caught.
Either way,
releasing Josuke's mother
was all part of the plan…
The perfect plan
to observe Josuke.
Oh observation…
That's what my Stand,
Misterioso, does.
Misterioso meticulously observes
Koichi Hirose and your mother,
as well.
JULY 15TH (THURS) 7:37 AM
God he really pisses me off.
I'll just help myself to his, then!
Josuke! So you are home.
You're here, right?
THESE ARE YOUR PANTIES
No one is immune to fear.
You really shouldn't hide the glow
of fear or the tremors of dread.
The kind of fear that lies
deep in your soul
can never be wiped away…
Not for anyone.
Wh-Who are you?
How did you get in here?
My observations tell me,
when gripped with fear,
you tend to swallow your saliva…
All people exhibit certain
unconscious behaviors
when in a state of panic.
Certain terror-induced quirks…
Did you know you do that?
I said who the hell are you!
I'm not giving you any money!
Get the hell out of here!
Do I look like a burglar?
I don't need your money.
In fact,
I feel like I should pay you.
I'm really quite enjoying myself.
Being the recipient of
so much attention is such a treat.
The attention you're showering me
with out of fear is wonderful.
GULP
Oh? Swallowed again, eh?
See? You just swallowed again!
So that really is
your mark of fear!
Once I discover your mark of fear,
my Misterioso can unleash
its invincible onslaught!
TOMOKO HIGASHIKATA
I've transformed
Tomoko Higashikata,
and Koichi Hirose into paper
with almost no effort a tall!
KOICHI HIROSE
When I gave Koichi a little startle
on his way to school,
I discovered his mark of fear
is a double blink.
It was quite obvious.
Yuya, for the second time,
where is the scent coming from!
I imagined that,
regardless of Josuke's toughness,
plopping his mother before his eyes
would almost certainly
stir pangs of dread…
Sure enough, there was
Josuke's very own mark of fear.
When scared Josuke
bites his lower lip!
The next time Josuke
reveals his mark of fear,
BA-DUMP
Misterioso will eradicate
Josuke from this world!
Yuya, you haven't taken
your eyes off my mom.
Could it be…
Is it this jacket?
Could he be inside this pocket?
I don't care
what kind of Stand it is,
I need to know
is it in this pocket?
Oh? Is he…
Is he gonna bite his lip?!
Come on, bite it!
Yuya, answer me! Is it in here?!
Damn!
Fear hasn't overtaken him yet.
Josuke, I never promised
I'd help you fight.
We agreed tracking only.
It's too freaky
to do anything more.
I agreed to this
cause you healed me,
but no way in hell am I
gonna be an idiot
and walk right into harms way.
I'm sorry,
but this guy freaks me out!
Then I'll have to
find out for myself.
Nothing there.
Both pockets are empty.
Other than this piece of paper…
The scent transferred
to outside the pocket…
Could it be…
Don't! I wouldn't open
that piece of paper!
EPISODE 33
JULY 15TH (THURS), PART 3